Nishinoya!
Hell yeah!
Ugh, I knew it.
Yeah, right?
Nishinoya has been going after Nishinoya ever since the second set started.
He's relentless.
Most servers tend to avoid Nishinoya unless they have something up their sleeve.
This is probably the first time he's faced the humiliation of being a target.
Nishinoya.
Hey!
I can't stop now, stop, stop
I can't stop now, stop
I won't be able to win
Oh, I don't want to do it
I can't stop now, I can't stop now
足りない事 足りない事
ねぇ 増えてるんだろ
Say, say 堂々
今と今向き合って
堪能するよ 現実
杏も甘以も全部
振不動 我往正面取ったり出したいな
I think it's interesting, I think it's fun
I don't want to stop now
I'm going to be perfect, I'll laugh
I'll laugh
I don't want to stop now
And Atsubumiya scores two consecutive service aces against Karasuno's Libero!
I totally thought he was going to get that one back up
I don't want to stop now
You don't want to stop now
You're ahead
Yes I don't want to stop now
I don't want to stop now
You feel it really an perseverance
particularly devastating. Plus, the Libero is the defense specialist. If he can't actually defend,
there's no point in him being on the court.
Nishinoya has talked us up more times than I can count.
I promise, I'll always have your back!
Now he needs us. What can I say to help him?
Nishinoya!
What the hell?
What's he doing?
Finger push-ups. That's the punishment he kept giving himself during practice.
Nishinoya must be desperate to keep himself calm right now.
This is awesome!
Nishinoya must be able to hit it very hard.
That receive was weak!
Asahi!
I won't be able to hit it very hard.
He went for the setter! On Tsumumiya with the first touch! But wait! Osamumiya has positioned
himself under the ball!
He's not even a setter and he pulled off a c-pass? And on a counter, too!
He's covering for his twin! No surprises here!
Got him!
It wasn't the setter who set that ball, Phil! Instead it was none other than his twin brother!
What just happened? He totally had that block!
Don't worry. I mean it. You're a fantastic blocker.
Sure, jackass.
They got another one!
What's going on with Tsuna? I don't remember anything special about his offense before.
Is he just in the zone?
Rintaro is a notoriously slow starter.
The only thing he does fast is control the opposing team's blockers.
But Rintaro's greatest weapon is his horizontal range. Let's say a normal kid is comfortable
with the ball anywhere in about this area. Rintaro hits all of this. And to generate the wide range
he does, arms and shoulders aren't enough. He uses his whole upper body, what they call the core.
Since he uses his whole upper body, the spikes stay strong. It's nothing like the weak taps you'll
get from just using your arm. Oh, I don't really get it. But it does explain all those times when
I was convinced the blockers had him. But suddenly the ball goes right past their defense!
Oh, you said he controls the blockers. What's that about?
Just watch!
Watch out!
Damn it!
All right, Asahi! Give us a good one!
Why is he so upset about our team messing up?
Go, go, Karasu no! Get it, get it, Karasu no!
Ah!
Yeah, another intense service ace in this fantastic matchup!
Karasu no serves haven't been their strongest in the second set,
so I'm sure they're hoping to turn things around here.
Alan!
Yeah! Suki, lock it down!
Two blockers!
Well done.
Nice kill, Rintaro! Yes, yes, Rintaro! One more time!
The better the blockers are,
the easier it is for Suna to control them.
Number 1
There! See what happened on that play!
Huh?
What?
Figure it out?
Hmm
Number 10 was totally in position to hit the cross shot
Suki reacted instantly and moved to stop him and
Kageyama quickly jumped right in to back him up
but 10
His approach and his positioning are both false. He lures the blockers over to stop a cross shot then changes tack in mid-air
He does that without giving up a single ounce of power on his spikes
Quick attacks for most middle blockers tend to be a bit more compact than other attacks
They try to hit the ball so that it's fast enough to get past the block
But our boy here as long as the set gets to him
Rantaro's quick attack is powerful enough to fight that block head-to-head. Oh
impressive
Yeah, man nationals are crazy
Come on guys. We just need to get them unsettled so they can't use their quicks put everything into your serves and spike
Oh
Hmm
Nishidoya
Nice another powerful sir Phil and the brilliant reception from Karasano
One touch cover all right left side
three blockers
Yeah
Yeah, that was an intense spike from Alan Ojiro the ball is right up in the net
Kageyama pushes it over
Here comes Ojiro from the left again
Shut him down
No slacking off
Yeah, three blockers
That one really packed a punch and even got past three blockers
It was up there. It might actually have gone above the block. Now Karasano looks for their chance to fight back
Yeah
But Alan Ojiro slams it into their court yet again
One man gets three spikes in a row and none of them was easy. He fought tooth and nail for that point Phil
Oh
Nice skill Alan
Jump jump Alan
One more time
Not yet specs
There was no win in that one and our boys know that perfectly well and more importantly can't give Ojiro a break not even a 32nd one
Their number four reminds me of Ushiwaka
But what makes this guy different from Ushiwaka is they've got him receiving
So we focus our serves on him and we actually have gotten quite a few aces from doing exactly that
It should be putting a lot of stress on him
Plus he's getting a ton of difficult sets to hit and we've been blocking him left and right
His exhaustion and irritation are building up just the way we want them to
I hope at least
I
Don't say that I'm not dead
We take Tsukushima out and put Sugawara in I guess that means hisashi won't be serving
Uh
I
Just got my 25th service ace in my head
Hey
You guys better not be thinking we can go ahead and lose the second set just because we already won the first one
We're gonna win this thing two to zero
Yeah
For Alan Ojiro I want you to lay on all the pressure you can
Blocks help but I want you serving at him
And I certainly won't be complaining if you get some aces
But really what we want to do is send him to his knees
I might only get to be on the court for 20
Maybe only five seconds
But I'm gonna use it to annoy the hell out of you
Front
Alan, you need to stay focused.
Yes, sir.
Now it's Anarazaki's turn to bring in a pinch server.
And it's the first year Hezkei Rizeki.
I spent all three years of middle school on the pinch.
But one time I came in as a pinch server, I potched it.
And that was that.
Crush that foe! Kill that foe!
If I mess this up, it's all over.
Just think about this point.
One point at a time.
A safe serve from Rizeki shouldn't cause too much trouble.
I got it!
What the hell is that, sir?
What are you even doing here, you ding-dong?
Nobody told you to just give the ball away!
We haven't been heckled in a while. Nice work.
What is going on?
That's cold. They're booing their own team.
But he didn't miss the serve.
So why boo?
That's Anarazaki's cheer squad from hell.
If a player makes a weak play,
members of the group heckle them about it relentlessly from up in the stands.
They like this every single game.
What?
But it's not like the poor kid's a professional.
So yeah, that was exactly why I told you you need to make it count, man.
When you're in a match, you always overthink things.
We don't need a server who just gets the ball over the net.
Whether we're winning or losing, this team needs more.
Right.
We'll be in a Herman.
Wait.
A no-touch ace!
Great speed, perfect placement!
No one could have touched that one!
He's here!
Chill, Kageyama!
What are you talking about?
As the name suggests, Kageyama, but chill!
Remember?
It's like when I pulled off a quick attack without closing my eyes!
Or when he got Tsukishima to jump higher!
I sensed it in him then, too!
It's basically when he's at the very top of his entire game!
That said, it's only his face that's calm.
Inside, he's as brutal as ever, so you must proceed with caution!
This mode often activates when he's confronting a powerful foe!
He sounded like an instruction manual there!
I can feel the electricity in the air!
Huh?
Inatisaki is calling their first time out!
We've seen some powerful serves today, Phil!
Yes, both schools have shown a wide array of strong attacks!
Just keep pressing the attack like you have been the whole set, but don't slack on your receipts!
I'm sure you're all getting tired, but I promise they are, too!
Things are working in our favor right now!
Could Kageyama's serves be the beginning of a Karashino comeback?
Just keep concentrating!
Yes, sir!
Yes!
He scores again!
That time it's a good one!
I'm not in front of his concentration!
Food!
One more time!
Get in!
Alan!
We may not be able to crush their spirits, but if we can annoy them just a little, if we
can get them to hit their spikes just a little more aggressively...
Left, left!
Three blockers!
We have a chance!
We can turn this around!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
That's what I'm talking about!
Yeah!
Oh, hey, so does that mean...
Exactly.
I was not a good out.
Go, go, Karasuno!
Damn it!
And the ball is sailing right back over to Karasuno's side!
Too fast!
Don't go getting a big head now.
Summon!
Yeah!
This time it's Alan Ojiro getting the point!
He's making his presence known as an ace!
That was an impressive dig from Atsumu as well!
Tobio Kageyama and Atsumu-mia are both excellent setters and candidates for the All Japan Youth
Team.
But as you can see, they don't have to be putting up sets for the sparks to fly.
Osamu!
Hurry up and finish this set already!
Also, I want to point out, I got way more aces than you today!
Would you please shut up?
Well, shit.
He might have hit that one a bit too hard!
It's way out of bounds, filth!
No way!
That flew?
That is not where the ball goes!
Yeah, right.
Like you've never done that before.
You just had to provoke him, didn't you?
Ah!
Osamu seems super chill, but he can still be pretty competitive sometimes.
Of course.
Just consider his brother.
Oh.
Shake up their psyches, even the tiniest bit.
And it'll throw off their plays ever so slightly.
It's in!
All those little irregularities start to build up.
Gen!
And then, the tide turns.
Sorry.
All good.
No worries, Asahi.
I'm sorry, guys.
Hey, we'll get all rhythm back.
Just try to stay calm.
Oh, what?
Oh!
Huh?
I don't know.